E-mail: marianne.p.gendron@gmail.com

Phone: (248) 739-5731

Digital Project Manager

Thanks to my 5 years of experience in numerous Marketing fields and my Master's degree, I confirmed my skills as a **Project Manager**. I specialized myself in the **digital marketing** 3 years ago. As I speak fluently French and German, I will easily fit in a multicultural environment.

Experience

French Bilingual - Digital Marketing Account Advocate

CDK Global - Detroit, Michigan

SEPTEMBER 2016- TODAY

In this digital advertising agency, I manage more than 30 active websites and provide digital marketing strategies to our customers. I provide analysis and recommendations for their website and their social media. We work as a team to manage the dealerships' needs and are able to advise them in their mid-term and long-term **digital strategies**.

- + I achieved 117% of my monthly goals from my first month
- + I represent my team concerning SEO inquiries and our new bilingual website platform called NextGen

Digital Project Manager

Eluère - Nantes, France

DECEMBER 2014 - MARCH 2016

In this advertising agency, I managed more than 10 active web projects at the same time and confirmed my skills as a manager. I have always been able to resolve encountered issues and find the right balance between customer's and agency's needs.

- + Realization of plannings, quotes, mock-ups and detailed specifications for digital projects
- + Managing the project team (to 6 persons) for website achievements

My best project with the agency? www.sepro-group.com (custom WordPress template): this website had to be reachable all around the world and available in 6 languages.

Digital project Manager

OCTOBER 2013 - DECEMBER 2014

As a Freelance, I have been helping companies in their web projects. I have never needed to do any advertising: my customers contact me via word of mouth.

My best website as a Freelance? www.ludiscape.de (custom website with PHP and HTML): this website has confirmed my PHP, MySQL, HTML and German skills. I have had the opportunity to develop freely the German market through web marketing solutions (web banners, social networks & partnerships).

Education

Master's Degree – Marketing Project Management – IAE de Poitiers

SEPTEMBER 2011 - SEPTEMBER 2013

Studied: Marketing Project Management, market studies, communication strategy, international marketing

Bachelor's Degree – Management Science - IAE de Poitiers

SEPTEMBER 2010 - SEPTEMBER 2011

Studied: Marketing, communication, management, statistics and accounting

Franco-German expert certification DAAD - Ruhr Universität Bochum

SEPTEMBER 2009 - FEBRUARY 2010

Selection of 30 students, based on scholastic records

Studied: Marketing, German law class, translation, economic and social politics

1st / 2d year of Bachelor Degree Foreign Languages: English and German – UFR d'Angers

SEPTEMBER 2008 - JUNE 2010

English, German and Japanese

Studied: Translation, marketing, commercial law class and economic sciences

Skills & Certifications*

Languages

- + English & French: fluent
- + German: Full professional proficiency

Information Technology

- + Microsoft Office Suite
- + Google tools (Google AdWords*, Google Analytics)
- Website development and administration (HTML5 & CSS3*, PHP*, MySQL*, JavaScript*, WordPress)
- + Social Media (Sprout Social, Google+, YouTube, Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest & Instagram)